http://www.clavey.com/privacy-notice/

Sale
Home »
Privacy Notice - Clavey Paddlesports
Privacy Notice
Privacy Notice
We could have gotten some lawyers to write up our privacy notice and have it go on and on until the chickens came home but that’s just not like us. It’s pretty simple here at Clavey. When you place an order at Clavey you will be providing us with some basic personal information; name, address, email, phone, etc. We then put that information into our database so we can have it handy when you place another order. If, in the ordering process, you decide to sign up on our email list you will receive (at the most) one email a week informing you of any specials, new products, news or events. We will never, never EVER share your personal information with anyone – no affiliates, no research groups, political parties, etc – nada, nunca, no one! The only exception to this is if someone – Warren Buffet for example – decides to buy Clavey for a very large sum of money and in that case we would have to transfer our database to the new owner (who would have to be as cool or cooler than us).
Children
Clavey does not knowingly sell or collect information from children under 13. So if you’re under 13 feel free to check out the site but don’t even think about trying to place an order or we’ll tell your parents on you.
Cookies
We like cookies with milk, or a nice dark oatmeal stout, and our web server likes them to, so for a more satisfying shopping experience please have cookies enabled in your web browser.
Like Us On Facebook Clavey Paddlesports
Follow Us On Instagram
claveypaddlesports
Locally owned and operated we carry kayaks, SUPs and rafting gear suited for all budgets. Join in on one of our tours & classes, or rent quality gear.
A Big Thank You to All of our Clavey Paddlesports
Beautiful night for a paddle. Photos by our awesom
Yay!!
Shop like a pro and head on over to
https://shop.
Load More...
Copyright © 2020 Clavey Paddlesports - Petaluma, Sonoma County, California
